DAVID BALDUS PAPERS (APAP329) 1965-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Material form the Defenders' Association of Philadelphia, 1985-2008; 12; 84.7
  - Charging and Sentencing Study Philadelphia Case Files, 1996-1997; 12.2; 33.4
    - Fred Miller 8903187311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Gene Miller 8405070911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Glenn Miller 7810038611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Hayward Miller 91053272, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - John Miller 8305339011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - John Miller 8207159011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Joseph Miller 8210162611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Kenneth Miller 8409079011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Gregory Millhouse 8812309711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Mack Mims 8402225511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Kevin Mines 8303309911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Charles Minor 8902356311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Carlie Mitchell 8101063211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Leroy Mitchell, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Mark Mitchell 8404050612, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Tyrelle Mitchell 9007034411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Richard Mitchum 8009248311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Marcus Mobley 9104402211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Roberto Montanez 8412028211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Derrick Moore 8304107211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Eugene Moore 8309174111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Freddy Moore 8305018611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Odell Moore 9208040611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Rodney Moore 2026 PHL 94, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - William Moore 8501100611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Jose Morales 95110871, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Salvador Morales 8210129211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Salvator Morales 8210159711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - William Moran 8111309611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Clarence Morris 8304070311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Kevin Morris 8207040911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Vernell Morris 9211131511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Howard Morrison 8304188911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Anthony Morton 92040616, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Jeffrey Mosley 8301216811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Anthony Moss 9007207011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Alonzo Mosteller 8609200011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Arnold Mulholland 8907335611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Arnold Mulholland 8907354011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Arnold Mulholland 8910083011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Derrick Murchins, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Craig Murphy 8405260811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Craig Murphy 8509252311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Craig Murphy 8401261211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Terrance Murphy 8301111211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - William Murphy 8212184111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Willie Murphy 9105318811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Bray Murray 8204029311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Clifford Murray 8108263511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Florice Murray 8312229511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Eugene Myrick 8611209611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Frank Narducci 8707348217, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Philip Narducci 8707348257, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Arthur Nash 8103212911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Ricardo Natividad 97040013, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - James Nero 8208342811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Nicole Newell 95100369, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Darryl Newkirk, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Ly Ngow, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Thelma Nichols 8705122811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - William Nieves 93100972, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Rasheen Nifas 9101437, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Angelo Nock 8811298411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Carlos Ocasio 95070169, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Kelley O'Donnell 9212208122, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Carlton Odrick 9001302311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - William Olafson 93012407, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Joseph Oliver 8506086411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Montrell Oliver 97040036, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Berto Ordaz 96080043, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Oscar Orr 8510060611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Edward Ortiz 8410023011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Emilio Osorio, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Lamont Overby 96100608, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Michael Overby 95010580, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - George Padilla 9005196111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Angel Pabon 98020790, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Confesso Pabon 8609170711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Richard Pacell 8209202911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Donyell Paddy 93078962, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Donyell Paddy 93078962 3139, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Jose Pagan 91060008, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Sussano Pagan 8103203611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Alex Pakalins 8105238211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Warren Palmar 8006120311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Bernard Palmer 9305077923, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - James Paluch 9006244411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Joel Pannell 8601068711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Pantelis Pantemis 8512109211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Paul Parker 94041045 No Penalty Hearing, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Derrick Parks 9202002211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Rashid Parks 9011211312, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Theodore Parks 9401323, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Kenneth Parnell 8412176011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Morris Parrish 8810467011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Roscoe Parrish 8305134011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Allen Patterson 8612287111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Christopher Patton 8503159111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Leonard Patterson 8903144611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Jerry Payne 9206152511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - John Payne 8505275411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - John Peay 8003241822, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Kevin Pelzer 8810317524, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Jamel Pendergrass 9102170811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Meredith Penn 8408159311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Tracey Penrose 7591991, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Al Peoples 8910449811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Eladio Perez Jr. 8302062611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Isadore Perez 8907014411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Marcus Perez 8908213822, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Nelson Perez 8711227511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Anthony Perkins 9005197411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Emmett Perkins 8507365211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Thomas Perrin 8611164111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Curry Perry 89041812, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Curtis Perry 9105099258, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Anthony Perisano 93020556, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Bruce Person 8206256111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Stephen Person 8904182822, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Edward Peterson 8611034811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Legrande Peterkin 8706229911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Otis Peterkin 8202078411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Warren Peterson 89062345, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Calvin Phelps 8906017611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Bortela Philisten 93070969, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Damian Philips 94110041, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Karen Phillips 8805346911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Sherman Phillips 8706070011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Michael Pierce 9008032511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Simon Pirela 8301214311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Heribert Pirela, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - John Pisa 8509158911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Chris Pitt 95120109, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Anthony Pitts 8905086911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Michael Pizzi 8608107211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Alfredo Pizzo 9103334911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Calvin Player 8212117611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Bernard Pogue, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Derrick Pointer 9110289811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Terrance Poles 8910450411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Eric Polk, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Frederick Pompey 8809169912, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Perry Poole 9003277911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Ernest Porter 8506224911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Howard Porter 9105045722, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Ernest Potts 8102224811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Alberto Prado 8411278111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Jeffrey Pratt 8902010011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Warren Preston 8701055411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Darryl Price, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Morris Price 9009107811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Barry Priester 9007231211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Gerard Prince 8912102711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Darrel Prosser 8305061311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Tawaine Prunty 9407082811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Raymond Pryer 8507037211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Theodore Pryzbyew 8503007011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Lamot Pugh 9002358811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Phillip Pulley 8612060011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Kerry Purnell 9210019711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Derric Ragan 9009261611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Derrick Ragan9008014111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Marlene Rahatt 9112298411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Karl Rainey 94120717, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Kyle Rainey 94070834, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Michael Rainey 9004197733, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Carlton Ransom 8301301811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Coley Ransom, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Clifford Ransome 8309263711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Leonard Ravenall 8702288211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Richard Rawles 7912122411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Dwight Reddick 8806275711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Jason Reed 8808043011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Leroy Reed 8801307611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Robert Reed 8908130811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Leonard Reel 7811167111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Elias Refile 8110196311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Anthony Reid 8810248211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Anthony Reid 8906025211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Anthony Reid 8907000811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Lloyd Reid 9104054611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Maurice Revels 93052548, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Pedro Reymoso 94050030, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Lawrence Rhodes 9009047711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Lawrence Rhodes 9009478 No Penalty Hearing, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Harry Riccobene 8406209411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Timothy Rice 96090623, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Frank Richards 9109362911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - David Richardson 93084894, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Michelle Richardson 9002042611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Tyrone Richardson 8404121412, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Joseph Rico 91013022, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Eric Riddick 9201413611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Charles Rideout 9107439111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Daniel Ried 86110366, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Arthur Rigney 7904145111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Emmanuel Rios 8912368993, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Miguel Rios 92103195, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Miguel Rios 9210317411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Emmanuel Riso 8912338033, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Johnnie Rivera 9006358511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Jose Rivera 9101014511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Renaldo Rivera, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Victor Rivera 9101240812, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - William Rivera 9609024311 No Penalty Hearing *Restricted*, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Frederick Rivers 9107159211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Delores Rivers 8803351923, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Paul Rizzuto, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Robert Robbins 8402019411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Leonard Roberts 8902127911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Lonnie Roberts 8903187911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - William Roberts 8606077711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Portie Robertson 8211111511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Andre Robinson 8802100411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Darrin Robinson 8710178512, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Eric Robinson 8112067011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Keith Robinson 8901316211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Lance Robinson 8510183612, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Roy Robinson 8808372911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Robert Robinson 8207181011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Sidnes Robinson 8206133711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Shannon Robinson 9012176811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Stephen Robinson 900711722, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Vernon Robinson 9100034914, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Wayne Robinson 9007111722, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Dennis Rodgers 92113465, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Paul Rodgers 9011338511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Alexis Rodriguez 8907162599, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Angel Rodriguez 89123396, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Jose Rodriguez 8301384611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Manuel Rodriguez 9302287811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Edgar Rogers 7904084311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Eric Rogers 8912317211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Florencio Rolan 8402289311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Saharris Rollins 8604058511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Felix Rolon 8403104922, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Bruce Romanoff 8405070311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Edwin Romero 19951827, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Stanley Rooker, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Wayne Roquamore 9001302011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Frank Rosado 8910081911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Raymond Rosado 9008015611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Bienvenido Rosario 8711036813, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Pablo Rose 8206209911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Warren Roseboro, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Stan Rosenthal 8606076911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Albert Ross 8201223111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Robert Rosser 9003391012, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Routha Roussaw 8909314211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Corey Rowe 9203178511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Malcolm Rowe 9107152811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Anthony Royster 9101238811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Denovian Royster 9107252211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Michael Rucker 9012178322, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - David Ruder 8802447225, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - John Ruffin 8501100911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Jamie Ruiz 8703359811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Jimmy Ruiz 8908212811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Sandra Ruotolo, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Larry Rush 8707087111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - George Russell 91111509, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Paul Russel 9106117811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Thavirack Sam 8907435911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Charles Sample 8902016611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - James Sample 9105174511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Enrique Sanabria 8303049511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Santiago Sanabria 9103321012, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - John Sanders 8402289711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Malachia Sanders 8711174411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Omar Sanchez 92040609, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Darnell Sanders 9203279411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - James Sanders 8907162579, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Raymond Sanders 8908211927, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Charles Sanford 8412029322, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Exor Santiago 9203189111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Fidel Santiago 9004201211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Jamie Santiago 95051182, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Jose Santiago 92092347, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Victor Santiago 8902365211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Wilfredo Santiago 8509022111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Paul Satterfield 8405261211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - James Saunders 8808274411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Thornton Savage 8512109822, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Kenneth Saxton 8010076311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Nicodemo Scarfo 8707348247, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Keith Scavo, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Wayne Schellin 9104238411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Edward Schleigh 8503320511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Mark Schultz 9101243811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - David Scott 8907258311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Gregory Scott 8608277011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Charles Scott 9012177311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Victor Scott 8308298711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Bernard Scott 96080507, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Steven Scott 92111298, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Derrick Scurry 8201224211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Willie Seals 8110125411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Russel Selby 8608148311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Ivan Serrano 8706367822, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Gwendolyn Shamberger 8907420711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Shawn Sharp 9105001611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Scott Shaw 8208275311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Virgil Shaw 9108039634, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Larry Shaw 8601193512, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Tracey Shaw 95030394, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Jerry Sheilds 93122057, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Kennard Short 8007089111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Derrick Simmons 8301304011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Bobbie Sims 8205007511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Bobbie Sims 8106298411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Rasheed Simpson 96110316, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Robert Singleton 8711271111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Anthony Singleton, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Edward Sistrunk 94011652, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - George Slater 9008204511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Elmer Slingerland 731985, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Lester Small 9010117711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Henry Smalls 8405261711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Andrew Smallwood 8912065711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Anthony Smith 8901011111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Derrick Smith 8302115111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Garnet Smith 8503321811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - George Smith 9012254211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - James Smith 8307178913, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - James Smith 8203465611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Karrie Smith 8901062411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Keith Smith 8312113811, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Richard Smith 9112033311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Richard Smith 9302117911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Robert Smith 8808101511, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Rodney Smith 8303309211, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Ronald Smith 8512108911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Ronald Smith 93124120 No Penalty Hearing, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Ronnie Smith 9112406411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - William Smith 8201068311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Yakoub Smith 9204000166, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Henry Smolarsk 7911160011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Willie Sneed 8406066911, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Willie Sneed 8406067411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Melvin Speight 9210362711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Morris Spence 8609339111, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - William Spencer 8108020411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Mark Spotz 16731995 No Penalty Hearing, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Vernon Steed 8701299311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Michael Stokes 91112699, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Lewis Stern 8706291411, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Darrin Stokes 9101014011, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Ralph Stokes 8203457611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Ralph Stokes 8203457611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Ralph Stokes 8203457611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Robert Stokes 8202173212, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Willie Stokes 8406066611, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Richard Stoyko 5271980 No Penalty Hearing, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Mildred Strickla 8512107311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Maurice Stroman 96080606, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Larry Stromberg 96050306, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - George Stump 8601191922, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Larry Sturgis 8609036711, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Shannon Sturgis 93053644, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Rogelio Suarez 9012057311, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Michael Sullivan, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 34)